One of my favorite flavors I've ever
made. Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is strawberry cheesecake. Let me
show you how to make. We're not actually
starting with the ice cream. We're going
to make the strawberry topping. To make
it, you're just going to grab some
strawberries and then toss them up with
a little bit of sweetener and a splash
of lemon juice. You can use either
frozen or fresh strawberries. I use
frozen. The key here is to get these in
the fridge ASAP. They need a few hours
to merate and soften. Now, getting into
the ice cream. This is similar to my
regular strawberry base, but we're
adding in some cream cheese to give it
that cheesecake flavor. And because I
know you're already typing it, yes, you
can use cheesecake jell-o pudding mix,
but no, it will not be as good. The
cream cheese adds a little bit of fat
and gives it a thicker consistency.
Honestly, just more decadent and more
like cheesecake in my opinion. After
that initial light ice cream cycle,
you're going to take it out, scrape from
the sides with a butter knife, throw it
back in on the respin setting, and if it
comes out looking like this, with a
massive hole in the middle, congrats,
you did it right. So now we can hollow
out that hole even more to give a nice
crater for our strawberry topping to go
into. Think of it kind of like a Ben &
Jerry's core flavor. And you can just
finish it off with some crumbled graham
cracker.
>> That's good. Mhm. That's a really good
contrast of um textures.
>> Consistency is good. Let's try the ice
cream. Ice cream's good. Big chunks of
strawberry.
Very good. And for once, I got to agree
with my parents because honestly, this